const quizArr = [
    {
        question:"What is the 6<sup>th</sup> planet in the solar system?",
        opt1:"Jupiter",
        opt2:"Saturn",
        opt3:"Earth",
        opt4:"Neptune",
        answer:"Saturn"
    },
    {
        question:"The addition of which of these notes is of maximum value?",
        opt1:"Four notes of Rs. 500",
        opt2:"Thirty notes of Rs. 100",
        opt3:"Ten notes of Rs. 50",
        opt4:"One note of Rs. 2000",
        answer:"Thirty notes of Rs. 100"
    },
    {
        question:"According to Hindu mythology, Ravana was a great devotee of which of these deities?",
        opt1:"Lord Ganesh",
        opt2:"Lord Indra",
        opt3:"Lord Vishnu",
        opt4:"Lord Shiva",
        answer:"Lord Shiva"
    },
    {
        question:"What does the 'S' in SUV, a type of car, stand for?",
        opt1:"Sport",
        opt2:"Sense",
        opt3:"Speed",
        opt4:"Spirit",
        answer:"Sport"
    },
    {
        question:"In the context of light, if we mix all the seven colours of the rainbow, what would the resultant colour be?",
        opt1:"White",
        opt2:"Black",
        opt3:"Maroon",
        opt4:"Dark Blue",
        answer:"White"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of the following countries' flag does not have a star on it?",
        opt1:"Australia",
        opt2:"Belgium",
        opt3:"New Zealand",
        opt4:"China",
        answer:"Belgium"
    },
    {
        question:"Which country is home to the tallest mountain in the world, Mount Everest?",
        opt1:"Nepal",
        opt2:"China",
        opt3:"India",
        opt4:"Japan",
        answer:"Nepal"
    },
    {
        question:"Who, during his days in prison, wrote an essay titled 'Why i am Atheist'?",
        opt1:"Bhagat Singh",
        opt2:"Michael Madhusudan Dutt",
        opt3:"Subhas Chandra Bose",
        opt4:"Motilal Nehru",
        answer:"Bhagat Singh"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these numbers features in the multiplication tables of both 3 and 9",
        opt1:"24",
        opt2:"30",
        opt3:"39",
        opt4:"18",
        answer:"18"
    },
    {
        question:"The year mentioned in which of these Hindi film titles is a reference to the year of the Quit India Movement?",
        opt1:"23rd March 1931: Shaheed",
        opt2:"1920: Evil Returns",
        opt3:"1942: A Love Story",
        opt4:"Summer 2007",
        answer:"1942: A Love Story"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these legendary characters released a genie by rubbing a magical lamp?",
        opt1:"King Arthur",
        opt2:"Hercules",
        opt3:"Pocahontas",
        opt4:"Aladdin",
        answer:"Aladdin"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these ancient peoples are known for mummifying bodies?",
        opt1:"Romans",
        opt2:"Vikings",
        opt3:"Egyptians",
        opt4:"Greeks",
        answer:"Egyptians"
    },
    {
        question:"Which sacred Hindu scripture contains a collection of hymns and verses dedicated to various deities?",
        opt1:"Ramayana",
        opt2:"Bhagavad Gita",
        opt3:"Upanishads",
        opt4:"Rigveda",
        answer:"Rigveda"
    },
    {
        question:"Normally,with which of these does every sitting of the Indian Parliament start?",
        opt1:"Zero hour",
        opt2:"Question hour",
        opt3:"Legislative business",
        opt4:"Priviledge motion",
        answer:"Question hour"
    },
    {
        question:"Which of these animals gives its name to a road marking indicating a path for pedestrians to cross the road?",
        opt1:"Tiger",
        opt2:"Giraffe",
        opt3:"Zebra",
        opt4:"Vulture",
        answer:"Zebra"
    },
    {
        question:"Who among these is also known as Anjaneya and was born to Anjana?",
        opt1:"Lord Krishna",
        opt2:"Lord Hanuman",
        opt3:"Karna",
        opt4:"Bhishma",
        answer:"Lord Hanuman"
    },
    {
        question:"If sangeeta is Amar's father's sister, what would be the relationship between Sangeeta and Amar?",
        opt1:"Behen-Bhai",
        opt2:"Chachi-Bhatija",
        opt3:"Maami-Bhanja",
        opt4:"Bua-Bhatija",
        answer:"Bua-Bhatija"
    },
    {
        question:" 'Commissioner', 'superintendent', and 'inspector' are ranks found in which of these?",
        opt1:"Army",
        opt2:"Police Force",
        opt3:"Navy",
        opt4:"Air Force",
        answer:"Police Force"
    },
    {
        question:"Various shades of green can be found in the logo of which Microsoft application?",
        opt1:"Word",
        opt2:"PowerPoint",
        opt3:"Excel",
        opt4:"Skype",
        answer:"Excel"
    },
    {
        question:"Which Indian president was the first ever Principal Scientific Advisor to the Government of India?",
        opt1:"Pranab Mukherjee",
        opt2:"Dr APJ Abdul Kalam",
        opt3:"Ram Nath Kovind",
        opt4:"Dr S Radhakrishnan",
        answer:"Dr APJ Abdul Kalam"
    }
];